{
"question": "山",
"answer": "やま"
},
{
"question": "窓",
"answer": "まど"
},
{
"question": "動物",
"answer": "どうぶつ"
},
{
"question": "夜",
"answer": "よる"
},
{
"question": "料理",
"answer": "りょうり"
},
{
"question": "夏",
"answer": "なつ"
},
{
"question": "新聞",
"answer": "しんぶん"
},
{
"question": "公園",
"answer": "こうえん"
},
{
"question": "意味",
"answer": "いみ"
},
{
"question": "自転車",
"answer": "じてんしゃ"
},
{
"question": "足",
"answer": "あし"
},
{
"question": "電車",
"answer": "でんしゃ"
},
{
"question": "散歩",
"answer": "さんぽ"
},
{
"question": "声",
"answer": "こえ"
},
{
"question": "朝",
"answer": "あさ"
},
{
"question": "歌",
"answer": "うた"
},
{
"question": "靴",
"answer": "くつ"
},
{
"question": "箱",
"answer": "はこ"
},
{
"question": "机",
"answer": "つくえ"
},
{
"question": "帽子",
"answer": "ぼうし"
},
